<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My city</string>
    <string name="Coffee_shop">Coffee Shop</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="theatre">Movie Theatre</string>
    <string name="mall">Malls</string>
    <string name="coffee1">Star Bucks</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping centre</string>
    <string name="star_bucks">Star bucks</string>
    <string name="starbucks_description">Every day, we go to work hoping to do two things: share great coffee with our friends and help make the world a little better. It was true when the first Starbucks opened in 1971, and it’s just as true today.\nBack then, the company was a single store in Seattle’s historic Pike Place Market. From just a narrow storefront, Starbucks offered some of the world’s finest fresh-roasted whole bean coffees. The name, inspired by Moby Dick, evoked the romance of the high seas and the seafaring tradition of the early coffee traders.\n\nIn 1981, Howard Schultz (Starbucks chairman, president and chief executive officer) first walked into a Starbucks store. From his first cup of Sumatra, Howard was drawn into Starbucks and joined a year later.\n\nA year later, in 1983, Howard travelled to Italy and became captivated by Italian coffee bars and the romance of the coffee experience. He had a vision to bring the Italian coffeehouse tradition back to the United States. A place for conversation and a sense of community. A third place between work and home. He left Starbucks for a short period of time to start his own Il Giornale coffeehouses and returned in August 1987 to purchase Starbucks with the help of local investors.\n\nToday, with store in more than 75 markets, Starbucks is the premier roaster and retailer of speciality coffee in the world. And with every cup, we strive to bring both our heritage and an exceptional experience to life.</string>
    <string name="coffee_bean">Coffee bean</string>
    <string name="coffee_bean_description">A coffee bean shop is a cozy, inviting space dedicated to the sale and appreciation of high-quality coffee beans. The shop offers a variety of beans sourced from different regions around the world, each with its own distinct flavor profile, such as fruity, nutty, or chocolatey undertones. These beans are typically sold by weight and can be either whole or ground, depending on customer preference.\n\nIn addition to selling coffee beans, the shop often provides educational resources, such as information on brewing techniques, roasting methods, and the origins of the beans. The atmosphere is usually warm and aromatic, with the rich smell of freshly roasted coffee permeating the air. The shop may also offer tastings, allowing customers to sample different beans before making a purchase.</string>
    <string name="love_coffee">Love cafe</string>
    <string name="love_coffee_description">A Love Café Shop is a cozy, romantic-themed coffee spot designed to create a warm, welcoming ambiance for couples, friends, or individuals looking to enjoy a peaceful atmosphere. The décor typically features soft lighting, comfortable seating, and intimate nooks adorned with flowers, heart-shaped motifs, and calming colors like pastels or deep reds. \n\nThe menu offers a variety of specialty coffees, teas, and desserts, with items like heart-shaped pastries, latte art with love symbols, and signature drinks named after romantic themes. Soft background music, often jazz or acoustic, sets a relaxed tone, inviting guests to linger over conversations or savor a good book. The café may also host themed events, like date nights, poetry readings, or live acoustic performances, enhancing the overall experience of connection and affection.\n\nIt’s a perfect space to celebrate love, self-care, or simply enjoy quality time in a serene, heartfelt environment.</string>
    <string name="coffee_house">Coffee House</string>
    <string name="coffee_house_description">Come in and enjoy the smell of freshly brewed coffee. At Coffee House, we make every cup with care, using high-quality beans. Whether you\'re grabbing a quick espresso, enjoying a smooth cappuccino, or trying one of our teas, each drink will help you relax and enjoy the moment.\n\nOur cozy space is great for chatting with friends, reading a book, or getting some work done. Try one of our fresh pastries or snacks with your drink, and you’ll feel right at home.\n\nFrom morning coffee to afternoon breaks, Coffee House is the perfect spot to relax and recharge. We can’t wait to serve you!</string>
    <string name="spell_coffee">Spell Coffee</string>
    <string name="spell_coffee_description">Step into a magical world where every cup of coffee is brewed with a touch of enchantment. At Enchanted Brews, we blend the art of coffee making with a sprinkle of magic. Our beans are carefully selected and roasted to perfection, creating potions that will awaken your senses.\n\nWhether you\'re seeking an energizing espresso, a calming herbal tea, or one of our signature spellbinding lattes, each drink is crafted to lift your spirit and cast a spell of relaxation. Pair your drink with one of our mystical pastries, baked fresh daily with secret ingredients for an extra dose of wonder.\n\nOur cozy, spellbound atmosphere is perfect for studying ancient texts, meeting fellow witches and wizards, or simply enjoying a quiet moment with a magical brew.\n\nCome to Enchanted Brews and discover the magic in every cup. Your next enchanting experience awaits!</string>
    <string name="Steamy_Cup">Steamy Cup Cafe</string>
    <string name="steamy_cup_description">Welcome to Steamy Cup Cafe, where every cup of coffee is served with warmth and charm. Our shop specializes in creating the perfect blend of rich, aromatic coffee, carefully brewed to delight your senses. Whether you\'re in the mood for a strong espresso, a creamy cappuccino, or a soothing tea, each sip will make you feel right at home.\n\nThe cozy atmosphere at Steamy Cup Cafe is ideal for a relaxing break, whether you\'re catching up with friends or enjoying some quiet time. Pair your coffee with our freshly baked treats, and let the comforting environment work its magic.\n\nCome by Steamy Cup Cafe, where great coffee and good vibes are always brewing!
    </string>
    <string name="black_thunder">Black Thunder</string>
    <string name="vgp">VGP Universal Kingdom</string>
    <string name="adventure_park">Adventure Park</string>
    <string name="cultus_park">Destination Cultus Theme Park</string>
    <string name="jolly_land">Jolly Land</string>
    <string name="black_thunder_description">Black Thunder Theme Park is a popular amusement park located in India, known for its diverse range of thrilling rides and attractions. Situated in the city of Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, Black Thunder is set against a picturesque backdrop of the Western Ghats. The park offers a blend of water rides, roller coasters, and entertainment options for visitors of all ages.\n\nDescription:\n\nBlack Thunder Theme Park is a premier entertainment destination nestled in the lush landscapes of Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu. Renowned for its exciting rides and attractions, the park caters to thrill-seekers and families alike. From adrenaline-pumping roller coasters to relaxing water slides, Black Thunder ensures a fun-filled experience for all guests. The park’s highlights include a vast wave pool, a lazy river, and various themed zones designed to keep visitors entertained throughout the day. Surrounded by the scenic beauty of the Western Ghats, Black Thunder provides a refreshing escape from the everyday hustle, making it a must-visit attraction for adventure enthusiasts and families seeking a memorable day out.</string>
    <string name="vgp_description">VGP Universal Kingdom is a renowned amusement and water park located on East Coast Road, Injambakkam, Chennai. Spanning a large area, it offers a wide array of thrilling rides, water slides, and family-friendly attractions, making it a popular destination for visitors of all ages.\n\nThe park features exciting roller coasters, a spooky horror house, and adrenaline-pumping rides like the Top Gun and Tornado. For those seeking a more relaxed experience, the park also has a serene Lazy River and a family raft ride. Additionally, the water park section, known as Aqua Kingdom, includes wave pools and slides like the Aqua Racer, ensuring plenty of splash-filled fun.\n\nOne of the key highlights is the Snow Kingdom, which allows guests to experience snow-themed activities, making it a unique attraction in Chennai. For younger visitors, there\'s a dedicated kids\' zone with gentle rides like the Tiny Tots Express and the Circus Train. The park is also home to a petting zoo and a historic section featuring Paneer Fort, complete with Chola-style architecture.</string>
    <string name="adventure_park_description">Searched 6 sites\n\nAdventure parks are recreational venues that provide a variety of physically engaging activities designed for both fun and fitness. These parks often feature obstacle courses, rock climbing, zip lines, bouldering, rope climbing, and more. They cater to different skill levels and ages, offering both individual challenges and team-building experiences. Some parks, like Airtopia Adventure Parks, even take the excitement indoors, combining trampoline parks, high ropes, and warrior courses with family-friendly amenities like cafés, arcades, and party zones.\n\nAdventure parks focus on delivering an immersive and dynamic environment, allowing visitors to test their physical limits, whether through climbing walls, navigating aerial obstacles, or soaring through the sky on a zip line. Many parks also incorporate safety measures like harnesses and belay systems to ensure a safe yet thrilling experience</string>
    <string name="cultus_park_description"><![CDATA[Cultus Lake Waterpark is a haven for water enthusiasts, offering a variety of attractions that appeal to both families and thrill-seekers. With over 25 slides, the park features some of the most exciting water rides in the region, including the \"Valley of Fear,\" a freefall tube slide that provides an adrenaline-pumping experience, and the \"Bazooka Bowls,\" where you are spun around a large bowl before dropping into a deep pool. For a more relaxing time, the \"Adventure River\" lets visitors float gently through scenic settings, while families can enjoy attractions like the \"Turtle Pool & Slides,\" designed for younger children.\n\nIn addition to water-based activities, the park provides ample amenities for convenience and comfort, including dining options like the Espresso Hut for coffee and snacks, and \"Grab n\' Go\" for quick meals like burgers and pizza. The park also offers VIP cabanas, where guests can relax in a private and comfortable space near the action.\n\nCultus Lake Waterpark is perfect for a summer adventure, offering a mix of thrills, family-friendly fun, and relaxation​]]></string>
    <string name="jolly_land_description">Jolly Land Park is an exciting theme park designed for families and adventure seekers alike. It boasts a wide variety of rides and attractions, from thrilling roller coasters and virtual reality experiences to more gentle rides suited for younger children. The park’s lively atmosphere makes it a popular destination for day trips, offering something for everyone, regardless of age. Visitors can enjoy carnival games, bumper cars, and interactive play zones. The park also hosts live shows and performances, enhancing the entertainment experience.\n\nIn addition to rides, Jolly Land Park features several dining options where visitors can grab a quick bite or enjoy a full meal, making it a well-rounded destination for a fun-filled day. Parents appreciate the park’s focus on safety, ensuring a stress-free environment where kids can roam and enjoy the attractions​</string>
    <string name="kfc">KFC Chicken</string>
    <string name="domino">Domino\'s Pizza</string>
    <string name="wow_momo">WOW! Momos</string>
    <string name="pizza_hut">Pizza hut</string>
    <string name="star_briyani">Star briyani , Ambur</string>
    <string name="kfc_description">KFC India, part of the global Kentucky Fried Chicken chain owned by Yum! Brands, has grown rapidly in the Indian market since its first outlet in 1995. Known for its iconic fried chicken, KFC has become a leader in the quick service restaurant (QSR) sector in India. As of 2024, the brand operates over 1,000 outlets across the country, making it one of the fastest-growing QSR chains.\n\nKFC\'s success in India can be attributed to its adaptation to local tastes, such as offering a variety of vegetarian options and spicier chicken dishes to cater to Indian preferences. This has allowed the brand to penetrate various regions across the country, even as it competes with other QSR chains like McDonald\'s and Pizza Hut. Its major franchise partners in India—Devyani International and Sapphire Foods—have been instrumental in KFC’s aggressive expansion, helping to open hundreds of stores in recent years.\n\nThe brand’s dominance in the fried chicken market, combined with its effective marketing and store network expansion, continues to solidify its position as a favorite among Indian consumers, with Bengaluru, Delhi, and Mumbai leading in store density</string>
    <string name="domino_description">Domino\'s Pizza in India, operated by Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd., has grown into one of the country\'s largest quick-service restaurant chains since its launch in 1996. India is now Domino’s second-largest market after the U.S., with over 2,000 stores as of 2024, and the company plans to double this number to 4,000 within the next five to six years. This rapid expansion is driven by India\'s burgeoning middle class and increasing demand for convenient, affordable dining options.\n\nDomino’s in India has been a pioneer in digital innovations, accepting online orders since 2011 and using a robust delivery model to reach consumers across urban and rural areas. The company serves more than 200 million pizzas annually across 421 cities and aims to expand further into smaller towns</string>
    <string name="pizza_hut_description">Pizza Hut is a global pizza chain known for its wide variety of pizza options, including classic favorites and innovative new creations. Founded in 1958 in Wichita, Kansas, Pizza Hut has grown to become one of the largest pizza chains in the world. Its menu features not only pizzas but also pasta, chicken, and a selection of appetizers and desserts. The brand is recognized for its distinctive red roof design and its commitment to delivering a casual dining experience with a focus on quality ingredients and friendly service. Pizza Hut also offers various ordering options, including dine-in, carryout, and delivery, making it a popular choice for pizza lovers around the globe.</string>
    <string name="wow_momo_description">Wow! Momo is a popular chain specializing in momos, a type of Tibetan dumpling. Founded in India in 2008, Wow! Momo has gained a strong following for its diverse range of momo varieties, including steamed, fried, and tandoori options. Their menu also features fusion dishes, such as momo burgers and momo wraps, alongside traditional sides and beverages.\n\nThe brand is known for its focus on quality ingredients and flavorful fillings, which cater to both vegetarian and non-vegetarian preferences. With a commitment to offering a modern twist on classic recipes, Wow! Momo has expanded rapidly across India and into international markets, establishing itself as a leading name in the momo industry.</string>
    <string name="star_briyani_description">Star Biryani Ambur is a renowned establishment known for its authentic Ambur biryani, a traditional South Indian dish famous for its distinct flavor and aromatic spices. Originating from Ambur in Tamil Nadu, the biryani served here is characterized by its use of fragrant basmati rice, tender pieces of marinated meat (often chicken or mutton), and a blend of spices including cloves, cinnamon, and star anise.\n\nStar Biryani Ambur prides itself on maintaining traditional cooking methods and using high-quality ingredients to ensure that each serving is rich in taste and authenticity. The restaurant has built a reputation for delivering flavorful biryani with a balance of spice and subtlety, making it a favorite among biryani enthusiasts. Its commitment to culinary excellence and consistency has made it a prominent name in the regional dining scene.</string>
    <string name="pvr">PVR Cinemas</string>
    <string name="inox">INOX cinemas</string>
    <string name="ags">AGS Cinemas</string>
    <string name="imax">IMAX cinemas</string>
    <string name="rohini">Rohini silver screens</string>
    <string name="pvr_description">PVR Cinemas is one of India’s leading multiplex chains, known for providing a premium movie-watching experience. Founded in 1997, PVR has grown to become a major player in the Indian film exhibition industry, with numerous locations across the country.\n\nPVR Cinemas offers a wide range of films, from the latest Bollywood and Hollywood blockbusters to regional and independent movies. Their theaters are equipped with state-of-the-art technology, including advanced sound systems and high-definition projection. PVR is also recognized for its comfortable seating options, including luxury and recliner seats, which enhance the overall viewing experience.\n\nIn addition to its focus on cinematic excellence, PVR Cinemas often features amenities such as gourmet snacks, themed food and beverage options, and exclusive movie events. The brand is known for its commitment to customer satisfaction and creating a premium environment for moviegoers.</string>
    <string name="inox_description">INOX Cinemas is one of India’s premier multiplex chains, known for delivering a top-tier cinematic experience. Launched in 2002, INOX has rapidly expanded across the country, offering a wide range of films, including Bollywood, Hollywood, and regional cinema. The chain is celebrated for its state-of-the-art auditoriums, which feature cutting-edge sound systems, high-definition screens, and plush seating designed for maximum comfort.\n\nINOX Cinemas is committed to enhancing the movie-watching experience with luxury offerings, such as recliner seats, immersive sound, and even premium theater formats like IMAX and 3D. Their focus extends beyond movies, with a gourmet food and beverage service, allowing patrons to enjoy a variety of snacks and meals while watching films.\n\nWith its modern amenities, customer-focused services, and innovative approach to entertainment, INOX has become a preferred choice for moviegoers seeking a high-quality theater experience across India.</string>
    <string name="ags_description">AGS Cinemas is a prominent multiplex chain in India, known for providing a high-quality movie-watching experience. Founded in 2006, AGS Cinemas has established itself as a leading player in the Indian film exhibition industry with a growing presence across major cities.\n\nAGS Cinemas offers a range of films, from the latest Bollywood and Hollywood hits to regional cinema, ensuring a diverse selection for moviegoers. The chain is recognized for its modern facilities, including comfortable seating, advanced projection technology, and immersive sound systems that enhance the overall viewing experience.\n\nIn addition to its commitment to cinema quality, AGS Cinemas often features amenities such as gourmet food options, clean and well-maintained premises, and attentive customer service. This focus on delivering a premium movie experience has made AGS Cinemas a popular choice for audiences seeking both entertainment and comfort.</string>
    <string name="imax_description">IMAX Cinemas is renowned for offering an unparalleled movie-watching experience through its advanced cinema technology. IMAX, short for \"Image Maximum,\" is a company that specializes in high-resolution, large-format film projection systems, which provide a more immersive and engaging experience compared to standard cinemas.\n\nIMAX theaters feature oversized screens with a unique aspect ratio and superior image quality, including enhanced color and clarity. The sound systems are designed to deliver precise, multi-dimensional audio that complements the visuals, making the viewing experience more captivating.\n\nIMAX offers various formats, including IMAX 2D, IMAX 3D, and IMAX Laser, each designed to maximize visual and auditory impact. The combination of cutting-edge technology and innovative design makes IMAX Cinemas a popular choice for blockbuster films, particularly those with stunning visuals and complex soundtracks. Whether it\'s a high-octane action film or a visually rich documentary, IMAX provides a premium cinema experience that aims to transport viewers into the heart of the action.</string>
    <string name="rohini_description">Rohini Silver Screen is a well-regarded multiplex chain located in India, known for its commitment to providing a quality cinema experience. Established in the early 1990s, the chain has built a reputation for its state-of-the-art facilities and customer-focused services.\n\nRohini Silver Screen theaters offer a variety of films, including the latest Bollywood, Hollywood, and regional releases. The chain is known for its comfortable seating, advanced sound systems, and high-definition screens that enhance the movie-watching experience. They often feature a range of amenities, such as concession stands with snacks and beverages, ensuring that guests can enjoy their favorite films in a pleasant environment.\n\nWith a focus on delivering both entertainment and comfort, Rohini Silver Screen has become a popular choice among moviegoers seeking a reliable and enjoyable cinema experience. The chain\'s dedication to maintaining high standards in its theaters has contributed to its positive reputation in the Indian film exhibition industry.</string>
    <string name="arena">Arena Mall</string>
    <string name="Stylish_trends">Stylish Trends</string>
    <string name="shopping_market">Shopping Market</string>
    <string name="black_friday">Black Friday</string>
    <string name="shopping_mall">Shopping palace</string>
    <string name="arena_description">Arena Mall for Sports is a specialized shopping destination dedicated to sports enthusiasts. It offers a wide range of sporting goods and apparel from leading brands, including athletic footwear, clothing, and equipment for various sports like soccer, basketball, tennis, and more. The mall often features dedicated sections for different sports, along with interactive areas where customers can test out products.\n\nIn addition to retail stores, Arena Mall for Sports might host events such as product launches, sports demonstrations, and fitness workshops. Its layout is typically designed to create an engaging and dynamic shopping experience, with a focus on providing top-quality gear and fostering a community of sports lovers.</string>
    <string name="stylish_trends_description">Stylish Trends is a retail destination or concept focusing on the latest in fashion and design. It offers a curated selection of apparel, accessories, and lifestyle products that reflect current trends and timeless style. The store typically features collections from both established and emerging designers, providing customers with a diverse range of fashion-forward options.\n\nThe ambiance of Stylish Trends is usually chic and modern, with carefully designed interiors that complement the fashion pieces on display. In addition to clothing and accessories, Stylish Trends may offer style consultations, fashion events, and seasonal collections to keep its offerings fresh and relevant. The aim is to help customers express their personal style while staying ahead of the curve in fashion.</string>
    <string name="shopping_market_description">A shopping market is a versatile and bustling venue where consumers can purchase a wide range of goods and services. It typically features various vendors and stalls selling fresh produce, meats, dairy products, baked goods, and often specialty items like gourmet foods or handmade crafts. \n\nShopping markets can be indoor or outdoor, and their atmosphere often reflects a lively and community-oriented vibe. In addition to food and groceries, many markets offer clothing, household items, and unique local products. They serve as a social gathering spot where people can explore diverse offerings, enjoy prepared foods, and interact with local vendors. Some shopping markets also host events, live entertainment, and demonstrations, adding to the vibrant and dynamic shopping experience.</string>
    <string name="black_friday_description">A Black Friday shop is a retail venue or event that capitalizes on the annual Black Friday shopping frenzy, which occurs the day after Thanksgiving in the United States. This day is known for its significant discounts and promotions, making it one of the busiest shopping days of the year.\n\nIn a Black Friday shop, you’ll typically find a wide array of products—ranging from electronics and appliances to clothing and home goods—offered at deeply discounted prices. The shop is designed to attract a high volume of shoppers with limited-time deals, doorbusters, and special offers that encourage quick purchases.\n\nThe environment during Black Friday is often energetic and bustling, with long lines and a sense of urgency as shoppers seek to snag the best deals. Many Black Friday shops also extend their hours, open early in the morning, or even start their sales on Thanksgiving evening to accommodate the high demand.</string>
    <string name="shopping_mall_description">Shopping Palace is a premium retail destination designed to offer a luxurious and comprehensive shopping experience. It features an elegant and spacious layout with high-end stores, boutiques, and international brands across various categories, including fashion, beauty, electronics, home decor, and more.\n\nThe environment in Shopping Palace is typically upscale, with a focus on providing exceptional customer service and a sophisticated atmosphere. It often includes amenities like gourmet dining options, exclusive lounges, and personal shopping services. The architecture and interior design of Shopping Palace are usually opulent, featuring high ceilings, stylish decor, and comfortable shopping spaces.\n\nIn addition to retail, Shopping Palace may host special events, fashion shows, and cultural activities, enhancing the overall experience for visitors. It aims to create a destination where shoppers can enjoy a blend of luxury, convenience, and high-quality products in one central location.</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="my_string">Hello</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back Button\n</string>
</resources>